敬这屁事也没得庆祝的一天
Here's to having nothing to celebrate.
其实今天是我生日呢
Actually, today's my birthday.
我就说吧 屁事也没得庆祝
Like I said, nothing to celebrate!
嘿 怎么不见Malloy?
Hey, where's Malloy?
他不能进来 我把他拴外边了
Eh, he couldn't be here. He got tied up.
禁止宠物入内
Woody会有好果子吃的
I'm going to get Woody for this.
天了噜
Oh, god!
你干嘛那个样子盯着人家?
Why are you looking at me like that?
你放口红的地方还真是奇特
That is an odd place to keep your lipstick.
怎么了 伙计?
What's the matter, buddy?
是不是自嗨还没缓过劲儿来呢?
Are you still bummed about your episode of intervention?
Steve 我们在这里是因为我们爱你
Steve, we're here because we all love you,
但拜托不要再戴着我们打飞机了
But you've got to stop jizzing inside us.
抱歉 可感觉真的爽死了
I'm sorry. It just feels so good.
爽死了?
Feels good?
老子都硬成石头了 你个死变态
I'm stiff as a board, you freaky bastard!
不啊 是因为Ethel
Nah, it's Ethel.
你也知道我多喜欢她 可她一直都当我是空气
You know how much I like her, but she won't give me the time of day.
现在又和天拉维总裁拍拖上了
Now she's dating the CEO of Skymall.
Skymall: 美国电子商务零售商
- 他到底有啥我没有的? - 能打电话的鞋?
- What does he have that I don't? - Telephone shoes?
你说得对 我根本没机会
You're right. I don't stand a chance.
down也有情绪低落之意
Steve 你必须在女人倒下时候趁虚而入
Steve, you got to get women when they're down.
我就那么做的 字面意思上
That's what I do, literally.
老太婆求救电话都会呼叫转移到我这儿
I get life alert calls forwarded to my phone.
我摔倒了 站起不来了
I've fallen, and I can't get up!
试试看能不能把内裤脱掉 我马上就到
See if you can slip your panties off. I'll be there in a minute.
看起来是个再普通不过的太阳能风扇遮阳帽
It may look like an ordinary fan-cooled solar safari hat,
但同时也是垃圾桶
But it's also a litter box.
天拉维
Skymall!
真是太叼了
That's amazing.
我前两天还和朋友说想要一顶能让喵星人拉屎的帽子呢
I was just telling a friend that I wish I had a hat that a cat could shit in.
天拉维
Skymall!
听我说 虽然我们只约会了几次 但...
Listen, I know we've only been on a couple of dates, but...
我真能看到我们的未来
I see a real future for us.
早想到你会这么说 所以我带了这个
I thought you might say that. That's why I got you this.
天啊 我的回答是 我愿...
Oh, my god! The answer is ye--
这是全世界最迷你的白噪音生成器
It's the world's smallest white noise machine.
什么? 那我们的未来呢?
What? But what about us?
玩完了 哥还不急着吊死在哪棵树上
We're done. I'm not ready to settle down.
不过你可以用这玩意儿生成暴雨的声音 好盖过你的哭声
But you can set this to heavy rain to mask the sound of your tears.
你要和我分手?
You're breaking up with me?
对
天拉维
Skymall!
给我拿来
Give me that.
Steve 你机会来了
Steve, now's your chance.
Ethel情绪比阿贝·维高达左边的蛋耷拉得还厉害
Ethel's lower than Abe Vigoda's left nut.
美国演员 现年93岁
她下瓶酒记我账上
Her next bottle's on me.
不不 会再联系你的 我保证
No, I'll call you, I promise.
我们刚在厕所来了一发 哥闪人了
We just [bleep] in the bathroom. I'm out!
你确定你这样子能开车吗?
Are you sure you're okay to drive?
你确定你能只管好自己的破事嘛草泥马?!
Are you sure you're okay to mind your own goddamn business?
我没事
I'm fine.
开得很好 Johnson 不要超出两边的线就好
You're doing good, Johnson. Just keep it between the lines.
诶 操蛋 Malloy 快过来开车
Oh, crap. Malloy, quick! Get behind the wheel!
Malloy
Malloy!
红色不是代表"停"嘛
I thought red meant stop!
漫迪字幕组倾情奉献
脆莓公园
♢ 症 ♢ 偏执绝非过错
♢ 井脑湿 ♢ MaxPayen999
♢ 旗木 联合译制
我昨晚都干了什么?
What did I do last night?
我进过你身子了
I was inside of you.
Steve到此一游
还有这里
上帝啊
Oh, god!
没事 Ethel 不要慌张
Okay, Ethel, don't panic.
你知道该怎么做
You know what to do.
听着 Steve 这事儿绝逼谁都不准告诉
Listen, Steve, you can't tell anyone about this.
为啥? 昨晚是我们生命中最赞的一夜
Why not? It was the best night of our lives.
不 绝对不是
No, it was not.
漂白剂
昨晚只是我"喝多酒犯了大错"的一夜
I had too much to drink, and I made a mistake.
给我老实闭紧你的嘴
So keep your mouth shut.
瞧瞧你把我当什么人了
What kind of guy do you think I am?
今晚 Steve Williams音乐剧《我上了Ethel》
♪ 我上了Ethel 我上了Ethel ♪
♪ I [bleep] Ethel I [bleep] Ethel ♪
♪ 我是上过Ethel的人啦 ♪
♪ I [bleep] Ethel, yeah! ♪
我干嘛花钱看这种东西?
Why did I pay to see this?
我没订过《牛皮癣周刊》啊
I don't subscribe to Psoriasis Weekly.
嗨 小甜心
Hey, love bagel.
美国演员
我这本维戈·莫特森的底裤写真咖啡伴侣读物应该放哪儿?
Where should I put my Viggo Mortensen up-skirt-shot coffee-table book?
Steve 你要搬来和我同居吗?
Steve, are you trying to move in?
我们做过爱 不是嘛?
We had sex, didn't we?
举行漫威英雄主题婚礼前 住在一起还不是早晚的事么
It's only a matter of time before we have our marvel heroes wedding.
Steve 醒醒吧
Steve, wake up!
一场酒后乱性不代表我们就是情侣了
Just because we had drunken mistake sex doesn't mean we're in a relationship.
是这样嘛? 那为什么我还买了情侣墓碑?
Really? Then why did I buy us those his-and-her tombstones?
2016年我们死于自杀式谋杀
We die by murder-suicide in 2016.
想想就兴奋
I'm so excited!
真不敢相信那个酒驾审理官竟判我做社区服务
I can't believe that DUI judge gave me community service.
你醉醺醺开进了法院
You drove to court drunk.
我喝酒是因为我紧张
I drink when I'm nervous
以及悲伤
And sad
以及抓狂
and mad
以及高兴
and happy.
♪ 我是酒鬼妥妥滴 哒哒哒哒哒嘟 ♪
♪ I'm an alcoholic, da-da-da-da-da-doo ♪
不 其实我有毛病
No, really, I have a problem.
没错 整整一晚把我拴在门柱上
Yeah. You left me tied to a post all night.
那条罗威纳狗现在一个劲儿给我发诡异语音
Now this rottweiler won't stop leaving me creepy voice mails.
让我跪舔吧
Let me suck it.
我搞不懂 Denzel
I don't get it, Denzel.
还以为只要在Ethel身体里播种 她就会甘心成为我的人呢
I thought once Ethel had some Steve in the beav,  she'd never leave.
至少你上过她了
Hey, at least you got some.
想想Connie多难受吧
Think about how Connie feels.
她也爱Ethel很多年了
She's been in love with Ethel for years.
我早就看淡了
Oh, I'm totally over it.
插个题外话 如果一定会在工作场所被谋杀
Off topic, if you guys had to get murdered in the workplace,
你们喜欢被自动步枪扫射 还是喜欢被大砍刀斩首?
Would you prefer an AR-15 or being hacked up with a machete?
我猜他们两样都喜欢
I think they want both.
怀孕 未怀孕
我还在你身子里呢
I'm still inside you.
都别进去
Don't go in there.
我... 拉了一大坨恶臭至极的便便
I, uh... Made a fat, smelly shit.
真是太尴尬了
So embarrassing.
远不及你曾和堪比一大坨恶臭便便的人打炮尴尬
Not as embarrassing as the fact that you made love to a fat, smelly shit.
这蘸糖棒尝起来一股尿臊味
Mmm, this Fun Dip tastes like piss.
那是验孕棒 你个脑残挫逼
That's a pregnancy test, you dumb son of a bitch.
我的天啊 Ethel怀上我的孩子了
Oh, my god! Ethel's gonna have my baby!
恭喜了 伙计 这下那婊子逃不掉了
Congrats, buddy! Way to trap that bitch!
没错 我真替你们感到高兴
Yeah, I'm really happy for you.
实话说 Steve 这事儿我想了很多
Actually, Steve, I thought a lot about this
就在过去的30秒里
In the last 30 seconds,
我觉得我还没准备好要个小孩
And I don't think I'm ready to have a kid.
但能容我说句话吗?
But don't I get a say?
我从没堕过胎 咱俩的就更不会了
I'd never abort a baby, especially ours.
抱歉 Steve 这事不由你说得算
Sorry, Steve. It's just not your decision.
凭什么? 我是孩子父亲
Why not? I'm the father.
有什么关系嘛? 我的身子 我做主
That doesn't matter. My body, my choice.
但Ethel 没了孩子 也就没有咱们俩了
But, Ethel, if there's no baby, there's no us.
一点不错 我已经和镇上最好的诊所约诊了
Exactly-I've already made an appointment at the best clinic in town.
Kuzniak医生堕胎车兼玉米卷车
堕胎/玉米卷一体车 就是镇子上最好的诊所?
An abortionmobile/taco truck is the best clinic in town?
是 这镇子操蛋透了
Yes. This town sucks.
堕胎是渎神之罪
Abortion is a sin against god!
生命无价 我反对堕胎 | 堕胎无罪 堕胎安全又合法
不 堕胎是民权
No! It's a civil right!
俺只是路过来买玉米卷的
I'm just here for the chimichangas.
你这是谋杀
This is murder!
俺来告诉你啥叫谋杀
I'll tell you what's murder.
这店子对调味干红辣椒漫天要价
The price they charge for a side of chipot-le.
Ethel 欢迎来到我的堕胎/玉米卷一体车
Ah, Ethel, welcome to my abortionmobile/taqueria.
或是按当地乡巴佬的说法 堕卷车
Or as the local yokels call it, the die-eria.
这里做安全的 对吧?
Uh, this is safe, right?
完全安全... 仅对女人 不对孩子
Perfectly safe... For the woman, not the baby.
等等 你不会就拿这脏不拉叽的厨具做吧?
Wait. You're not going to use dirty cooking utensils?
当然不会 Ethel 我会先给它们灭灭菌的
No, of course not, Ethel. I'm going to sanitize them first.
好了 准备就绪
Okay, ready to go.
在一切开始之前 我必须问你
Before you go through with this, I must ask,
你真的决意已定了嘛?
are you sure about this decision?
这是一个女人最难做的决定 但...
This is the hardest choice a woman can make, but--
抱歉 我在和客人说话呢
Sorry. I was talking to a customer.
好吧 就上牛肉卷吧
Okay, carne asada it is.
但得提醒下你 玉米卷用的沙司很热哦
But fair warning, the picante sauce is muy caliente.
西班牙语
没事 只要不热就成
That's okay, as long as it ain't hot.
褐丘精神病院
你不知道
You don't know.
你不知道 你不知道
You don't know. You don't know.
这天杀地灭的社区服务
Rackin' frackin' community service.
我才不想给一群脑子里养金鱼...
Working around a bunch of goddamn nut jobs
成天坐那儿自言自语的疯子做事呢
Who sit around and mumble to themselves.
你还好吧 先生?
Is everything all right, sir?
好得不得了呢 我爱死这些疯颠狂了
Oh, never better! I love these wacky bastards.
你是当爹的 是吧?
Oh, you're a dad, huh?
不容易 我儿子就因为我把他栓酒吧外边 对我大吼大叫
Yeah, my son yelled at me 'cause I tied him up outside of a bar.
你把他怎么了?
You did what?
别担心 我儿子是头会说话的熊
Oh, don't worry. My son's a talking bear.
不如我们坐下来说吧?
Why don't you have a seat?
这头会说话的熊...
This talking bear--
有没有唆使你去做伤害自己或者伤害别人的事?
does he ever tell you to do things that would hurt yourself or others?
你没开玩笑吧? 他成天就干这个
Are you shitting me? That's all he does!
有一次他把我整成了一条鱼
One time he turned me into a fish!
参见S02E12
了解
I see.
有时候他嘴巴贱到让我想剁了他
Yeah, he can be a sarcastic little asshole,
但我知道他是爱我的
But I know he loves me,
因为有一次我要和女朋友乘太空飞船离开地球
'cause one time I was gonna get on a spaceship with my girlfriend,
是他背着火箭背包把我救了回来
And he saved me with a jet pack.
参见S02E03
这里有个疯子
We got a nut job.
和你讲讲他给我当三级片导演那事吧
Let me tell you about the time he directed my porno.
参见S02E02
你特么地疯了吧?
Aah! Are you [bleep] crazy?
我可没疯 是你疯了
I'm not crazy! You're crazy!
人流积分卡
搞定 祝贺你 Ethel
And punchito! Congratulations, Ethel.
凑齐15次人流 送你免费鸡肉卷
15 abortions gets you a free chalupa.
谢了 但我永远不会忘记这段经历是多么痛苦
Thanks, but I'll never get over how traumatic that experience was.
再给你一张新的积分卡吧?
Would you like to start a new card?
好吧 拿上也无妨
Yeah, might as well.
Steve 你在这儿做什么?
Steve, what are you doing here?
给我和医生的交易收尾咯
Just sealing the deal I made with the Doc.
呃 什么交易?
Uh, what kind of a deal?
这事不太伦理啦 但他愿意给钱 而我... 见钱眼开
It's not exactly ethical, but he paid cash, and, well, I'm a whore.
Kuzniak医生把胎儿从你身体里抽出来后
See, after Dr. Kuzniak sucked the embryo out of your body,
转到我体内了
He put it in mine.
- 我怀孕了 - 什么?
- I'm pregnant! - What?
现在你进我身子了
Now you're inside me!
都别吃辣酱 我刚把恶心玩意给混进去了
Nobody eat the salsa. There's been a terrible mix-up.
肖恩·约翰牌童鞋? 谢啦 Denzel
Baby Sean Johns? Thank you, Denzel.
美国歌手吹牛老爹创立的服装品牌
也谢谢Connie 送我贴心的婴儿按摩棒
And thank you, Connie, for the baby massager.
嘿 快看 Connie把那玩意上的静脉都给你擦掉了
Hey, look at that. Connie rubbed all the veins off for you.
快看我的
Open mine!
我预感你们的孩子会是个妞哦
I have a feeling it's going to be a girl!
钢管舞免费课程?
Free pole dancing classes?
生孩子不带把儿 学钢管儿妥妥哒
If she's got a hole, she belongs on a pole.
这宝宝派对实在太棒了
What a wonderful baby shower.
我靠 Steve 这才过两天 你肚子就这么大了
Damn, Steve. It's only been two days, and you're already showing.
Kuzniak医生说我体内的睾丸酮会加速妊娠期
Dr. Kuzniak said the testosterone in my body will speed up the pregnancy.
Steve 你真特么混账
Steve, you're a [bleep] asshole!
所以我买了这件婴儿服
That's why I bought this Onesie.
我老爸真特么混账
我选择结束这段妊娠 你却夺走了我的选择权
I made a choice to end this pregnancy, and you took that choice away from me.
我不明白你干嘛这么不爽
I don't understand why you're so upset.
现在孩子都在我肚里了 生产什么的我全权负责
Now that our baby's in my body, I'll do the work for you.
你想堕胎不就是嫌这个太麻烦嘛 对吧?
That's why you wanted to get an abortion, right?
不 Steve 这是女人的决定
No, Steve, it's a woman's decision.
但孩子在我肚里了
But it's in my body.
你说过的 我的身子 我做主
Like you said, my body, my choice.
那不是... 不 你们几个 帮我主持公道
That's not--no. You guys, back me up here.
孩子在他肚里 Ethel
It's in his body, Ethel.
你也说过在谁肚里谁做主
You said that's all that matters.
给你 Ethel 这应该能让你高兴点
Here, Ethel. This should cheer you up.
我把你和Steve的照片用软件整合了下
I put your picture and Steve's picture into a computer program.
你们的孩子以后会是这模样
This is what your baby will look like.
美国演员乔纳·希尔
噢 天呐
Oh, my god!
不要
No!
听好 你个变态狗 都说了别再给我打电话了
Listen, you sick puppy, I told you to stop calling me.
给我滚远点 你个狗屎垃圾
Leave me alone, you piece of shit!
- 不 是我 Woody - 知道是你
- No, it's me, Woody. - Yeah, I know.
听着 那些王八蛋把我当神经病了
Look, these assholes committed me.
快来这里 告诉他们你会说话
Get down here, and prove you can talk.
我得离开这鬼地方
I've gotta get out of here.
我室友觉得他是尼古拉斯·凯奇
I'm roommates with a guy who thinks he's Nicolas Cage.
美国演员
好了 出动吧
Okay, let's ride!
《恶灵骑士》桥段
没准他就是尼古拉斯·凯奇 我吃不准
Or maybe that is Nicolas Cage. I don't know.
反正他疯到骨子里去了
Either way, he's [bleep] nuts.
你有没有被人拉到人行道上过...
Have you ever been dragged onto the sidewalk
还被暴打到直接尿血?
And beat until you pissed blood?
褐丘精神病院
好了 Malloy 说话吧
Okay, Malloy, start talking.
我保证他会说
I swear he can.
放在平时 他可是话匣子
Usually, he's a real chatterbox,
前提是他不是个记仇的贱人
When he's not being a spiteful dick!
拜托 Malloy 说话
Please, Malloy, talk!
- 吼 - Malloy 你个王八犊子
- Growl. - Malloy, you son of a bitch!
快证明老爹没疯 要不老子特么地拧掉你脑袋
Prove daddy's not crazy, or I'll rip your [bleep] head off!
简直是疯子里的标杆
Textbook psycho.
不对 我没疯 医生
No, I'm not crazy, doc!
我说真的 我养了只会说话的熊
I'm telling you, I have a talking bear!
我还有个会唱歌的小妹呢
And I have a singing beaver!
♪ 即兴演奏乐队Phish - Hello! My baby
♪ 你好宝贝 你好心肝 ♪
♪ Hello, my baby, hello, my honey ♪
♪ 你好 我那唱爵士乐的姑娘 ♪
♪ Hello, my ragtime gal ♪
快醒醒 Steve
Wake up, Steve!
Ethel 才凌晨4点
Ethel, it's 4:00 A.M.
这就对啦 有了娃儿是睡不成懒觉的
That's right. There's no sleeping when you have a baby.
我是爱放焰火的Jim小宝贝 你大爷的
I'm baby firecracker Jim, god damn it!
过了今晚再看你还想不想生孩子
After tonight we'll see who wants to keep this baby.
欢迎你体验当爹的感觉
Welcome to fatherhood.
帮我换尿布 爹地 便便都喷到背上了
Change me, daddy! I done shit up my back!
没事啦 咱的小宝宝马上就会变得干净清爽的
It's okay. We'll get baby nice and clean.
"婴"毛见过吗?
You ever seen a baby with pubes?
我一发怒就飙尿 因为我还不会用语言表达
I'm pissing 'cause I'm angry, and I can't express it in words!
你们说Woody讲的故事全都是真的?
So you're telling me all of Woody's stories are true?
对 Woody的确变过鱼 就在我生恶魔之子以前
Yeah, Woody was a fish just before I gave birth to the antichrist.
分别参见S02E12 S02E13
你生过恶魔之子?
You gave birth to the antichrist?
当然生过
of course she did.
对 小手手说得没错
Yeah, that hand's right.
事情就发生在我搞那个解冻的女野人之后
It was right after I banged that thawed-out cavewoman.
参见S02E01
我们可以走了吧?
Now can we go?
我还要帮我朋友Steve去买吸奶器呢
I gotta buy a breast pump for my friend Steve.
- 他怀孕了 - 男人怀孕?
- He pregnant. - A man is pregnant?
没啥大不了的啦 Steve身上怪事多了去了
Oh, that's nothing. All kinds of stuff happens to Steve.
他当过黑人 男同 还有女同
He was a black guy, a gay man, a gay woman,
分别参见S01E05 S01E06 S03E02
还当过吃自己大便的瘫痪人
And a quadriplegic that ate his own shit.
参见S02E05
咱没病吧?
See?
这些故事哪儿特么不正常了?
What is so crazy about these goddamn stories?
你不收钱是几个意思?
What do you mean you don't want the money?
我试过刁难他
I tried to be difficult,
但Steve这家伙把我照顾妥妥的
But that Steve feller took good care of me!
他肯定会是个好父亲的
He's gon' be a real good daddy.
看来老娘只有亲自下手了
Guess I'll have to take matters into my own hands.
Steve 咱俩谈谈
Steve, we need to talk.
就这样 好惹火啊
Oh, yeah. That's hot.
这是要上杂志封面啊?
This for a magazine or something?
不 我用来自爽的
No, no, just for me.
现在弯下腰去 把小菊花露出来
Now, bend over and show me your pooterus.
Steve 我应该向你道歉
Steve, I owe you an apology.
最近我对你实在不好 但看着你这个样子
I've been horrible to you lately, but seeing you like this...
或者又是这个样子
Oh, and like that...
这个倒真不怎么样
And not so much that one.
让我意识到 我的确想陪着你把孩子生下来
But it makes me realize that I do want to have this baby with you.
太棒了 Ethel
That's great, Ethel.
那咱俩去参加一些绝对安全的家庭娱乐活动 你觉得怎么样?
So what do you say you and I go on some perfectly safe family fun activities?
流产飞车
锈衣架工厂
废衣架 (坊间流传可用衣架直接自己堕胎)
你不知道 你不知道
You don't know. You don't know.
老子当然不知道
Of course I don't know.
这个游戏就叫"猜猜看"啊 混蛋
It's called "guess who," mother[bleep].
Connie在哪? 我们得谈谈
Where's Connie? We need to talk.
我看她刚交了个新朋友
I think she made a new friend.
好哎 咱们要去印度啦
Whee! We're going to India!
- 好哎好哎好哎 - 够了 别再疯了
- Oh, boy! Oh, boy! Oh, boy! - All right, you cuckoos.
咱们该从这鬼地方逃出去了
It's time to bust out of this nest.
- 为毛啊? - 咱们先...
- Why? - So let's--
居然还问我为毛? 咱都特么进了精神病院了
What do you mean why? We're in a goddamn mental institution.
- 这儿挺不错的啊 - 是啊 我也喜欢
- Aw, I like it here. - Yeah, I like it too.
虽然有点凉啦 但...
I mean, it's a little cold, but...
凉? 你就抱怨这个? 只是凉而已?
Cold? That's your complaint? It's cold?
管你俩喜不喜欢都得跟老子逃出去
You two are busting out whether you like it or not.
计划是这样的
So here's the plan.
首先 咱们得在墙里挖条隧道
First, we're going to tunnel through the wall
用这小勺
With this spoon.
然后顺着排雨沟一路爬到停车场
Then we'll crawl through the storm drains until we get to the parking lot.
Connie负责麻翻警卫 同时Denzel去偷车
Connie will then chloroform the guards as Denzel hijacks a car,
咱们开车撞开大门 冲向自由
Which we'll use to bust through the gates and drive ourselves to freedom.
赶紧的 开搞吧
Now, let's do this!
诶 操蛋
Oh, shit!
想逃跑是吧?
Trying to escape, huh?
带他去...
Take him to...
特殊治疗室
The special treatment room.
特殊治疗室? 听起来好别致喔
Special treatment room? That sounds awesome.
我倒是希望能有个新室友
I hope this means I get a new roommate.
- 生命无罪 - 堕胎无罪
- Pro-life! - Pro-choice!
脆莓医疗中心
别走 等一下 这哥们是怀孕了么?
Hold on! Wait a minute! Is that a pregnant dude?
老天爷啊 这简直是对上天的亵渎
Dear lord! It's an abomination to god!
他应该堕掉
He should abort it.
不对 他不该堕 这是科学的奇迹
No, he shouldn't! It's a miracle of science!
- 堕胎无罪 - 生命无价
- Pro-choice! - Pro-life!
死胎 死胎 死胎
Dead baby, dead baby, dead baby.
- 有心跳了喔 - 我靠
- We have a heartbeat. - Damn it!
老天爷 我擦嘞
[bleep] you, god.
我是说"好哎"
I mean yay.
生活太美妙了 Ethel
Isn't this wonderful, Ethel?
参加过那些夫妻牵手活动之后
And after all that couple stuff we did,
咱俩更亲密无间了
You and I are even closer.
Steve 我不想要这个孩子 我从没想过要孩子
Steve, I don't want this baby! I never wanted this baby!
苍天啊 我都把你推下楼梯 还摔在一堆衣架上了
For god's sake, I pushed you down a flight of stairs into a pile of coat hangers!
如果是男孩 咱们叫他"神秘吸血鬼"如何?
If it's a boy, could we name him "Dracula Untold"?
出自2014年同名吸血鬼电影
不是你的原因 Steve
It's not about you, Steve.
我就是不想做母亲而已 永远不想
I just don't want to be a mother, ever.
我不想要这个孩子 就算是别人的种也不想
I wouldn't want this baby, even if it were someone else's.
你说得真是时候 这孩子就是别人的种
Funny you should say that, because it is someone else's.
这家伙的
This guy's.
我天拉维商城的家庭财富后继有人啦
I hear there's an heir to the Skymall family fortune!
壕哥 这是真的吗?
Rich, is this true?
没错 看我这款可进行DNA亲子鉴定的伏地魔壁挂 不会错了
Yes, according to my dna-paternity test/ lord voldemort wall display.
- 天拉维 - 我要当妈了
- Skymall! - I'm gonna be a mommy!
听说你怀孕的时候 我就知道孩子是我的
When I heard you were pregnant, I knew it was mine.
我的小蝌蚪可健壮呢
I've got strong swimmers,
全靠这款旅行装储精器
thanks to my travel-sized sperm-ometer.
精子活跃度: 强
嘿咻好帮手天拉维
Skymall after dark! Shh!
这也太扯了
This is bullshit!
你俩啥时候睡过?
When did you even sleep together?
我们去Epstein酒吧那晚啊
The night we went to Epstein's bar.
哈 那就不可能了
Aha! That's impossible
因为那晚Ethel是跟我睡的 记得吗?
Because Ethel slept with me that night, remember?
那晚的事我什么也不记得了
I don't remember anything from that night.
反正我们就是睡了 我可以证明
Well, we did sleep together, and I can prove it!
那晚爱爱时我录了像了
I videotaped the night we had sex.
好了 未来的Steve和未来的Ethel
Okay, future Steve and future Ethel,
你们硬了吗?
You guys hard?
必须特么的硬啊
[bleep] yeah, you're hard.
我要和Ethel做的事情
The things I'm about to do to past Ethel
会突破你们的脑洞极限
Are gonna blow your mind.
怎么回事?
What--what happened?
起来啊 昏睡Steve
Get up, past Steve!
天啊 他死了
Oh, god! He's dead!
你给谁发短信呢?
Who are you texting?
太好了 我没和Steve做爱
Yes! I didn't make love to Steve!
天啊 还有比这更糟的事情嘛
God, this couldn't get any worse.
天拉维
Skymall!
Woody 我来帮你摆脱幻觉
Woody, I'm going to rid you of your delusions.
我问你问题 如果你给我非理性的回答
If you answer my questions with an irrational response,
我就电击你
I will shock you.
你能做到的 Johnson 谎话混过去就行
You can do this, Johnson. Just lie your way through it.
我还给你接上了测谎仪
You're also attached to a lie detector.
如果你撒谎 我会电击你
So if you lie, I will shock you.
操蛋了
Oh, shit.
问题一 你是和一只会说话的熊一起生活吗?
Question one: Do you live with a talking bear?
是的 我没有 拿我没招...
Yes, I don't. Ha. That ought to--
你撒谎了
That was a lie.
好吧 我是
Okay, I do!
你这是说胡话
That was delusional.
你到底想要干嘛?
What the hell do you want?
我要帮助你
I want to help you.
再问你一遍 你是和一只会说话的熊一起生活吗?
Again, do you live with a talking bear?
如果我不回答呢?
What happens if I don't answer?
那你就有冰激凌吃了
You get an ice cream.
- 我能吃冰激凌? - 你说胡话了
- I get an ice cream? - Delusional.
谢谢你来 Steve
Thanks for meeting us, Steve.
我们想跟你谈谈代孕的事 天拉维
We want to talk about you being our surrogate. Skymall!
我有一些要求
I have some terms.
好吧
Um, okay.
再坏能怎么样?
How bad can it be?
- 我想让壕哥去死 - 做梦去吧
- I want Rich to die. - Not gonna happen.
问问无妨
Worth a shot.
死掉 死 死亡 瘫痪
"dead. Die. Death. Paralyzed."
Steve Steve Steve 我知道你很生气
Steve, Steve, Steve, I understand you're upset,
但如果你给我们当代孕
But as payment for being our surrogate,
我会给你十万块...
I'm prepared to offer you $100,000
天拉喂消费卡
In Skymall credit.
我唯一要的就是Ethel
The only thing I want is Ethel.
我知道我们一贯处不来
I know we don't always get along,
而且我的银行账户只是个被我射满精液的袜子 但...
And my bank account's just a jizz-stained sock full of pennies, but--
想不想再来一发啊 你个死变态佬
Would you like to make another deposit, you freaky bastard?
我想说的是 如果你愿意给我一次机会
Anyway, I know that, if you would just give me a chance,
我会让你幸福的
I could make you happy.
所以我才把这孩子放进我肚子里
That's why I put this baby in me.
哇 Steve
Wow, Steve.
真是太...
That's so...
悲伤了 那是不可能的
Sad that's not gonna happen.
一旦你生下这个孩子
Once you have this baby,
壕哥和我就会搬到他在日本的天拉维办事处去
Rich and I are moving to his Skymall offices in japan.
我要堕胎
I want an abortion!
Kuzniak医生 我要预约堕...
Dr. Kuzniak, I need to schedule a--
你怎么来这么快?
How'd you get here so fast?
我这是去大学呢
Oh, I was heading to the university
有点春假结束的善后工作需要我处理
For a little post-spring break cleanup.
来个巧克力塔?
Choco taco?
Steve 你不能堕胎
Steve, you can't get an abortion!
我当然可以 我的身子我做主
Yes, I can! My body, my choice!
他说得对
He's right!
但那孩子一开始是我肚子里的 所以仍然我说了算
But it was in my body first, so it's still my choice.
她说得对
She's right!
但那是我播的种 所以应该我说了算才对
But it was my seed, so I should make the choice for everybody.
- 有人觉得糊涂了吗? - 我糊涂了
- Anybody else confused? - Yeah, I am.
要我说 咱们把这小杂种灭了
I say we all agree to kill this [bleep]
然后去猫头鹰餐厅看那些女服务员露奶怎么样?
And go to Hooters and look at some titties.
我同意 我是同性恋
Sounds good to me. I'm a lesbian.
我也同意 我是个伪君子
Sounds good to me. I'm a hypocrite.
杀 杀 杀 杀 杀 杀 杀 杀
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
随你们的便好了
With pleasure.
但有个问题 我羊水破了
Just one problem: My water broke.
看来要等它生出来我再下手了
Well, looks like I'll have to kill this thing on the outside.
Steve 喘气 Ethel 握住他的手
Steve, breathe. Ethel, hold his hand.
Kuzniak医生 看看施瓦辛格在《威龙二世》里怎么生孩子的
Dr. Kuzniak, look up how Schwarzenegger gave birth in the movie Junior.
剖腹产
Ah, c-section.
片子看够了 我怎么才能接生孩子呢?
But enough about my theater seats. How do I get this baby out?
哇 这声音我从来没听过啊
Wow. Haven't heard that sound ever.
这冰箱不是自动填满的么?
Why isn't this fridge magically filling itself?
Woody 你忘了交电费了
Woody, you forgot to pay the power bill!
好吧 我得去疯人院救他出来了
Oh, that's right. I guess I have to spring him from that nuthouse.
我想进入你的身体
I want to be inside you.
为毛你那玩意还发光啊?
Why is that thing glowing?
开心树 开心树 开心树
Happy tree. Happy tree. Happy tree.
Woody是不是有点怪?
Does something seem weird about Woody?
- 没觉得 - Woody 把约束衣脱了 咱们走
- No. - Woody, pack your straitjacket. We're getting out of here.
不 我的心魔来了
Ah! No! The demon from my mind!
给我滚开 你不是真的
Get away from me! You're not real!
这是真的不?
Is this real?
- 耶稣大爷诶 - 有事吗 孩子?
- Jesus Christ! - Ha ha! Yes, my son?
嘿 医生 我的确会说话
Hey, doc. Turns out I can talk.
所以把这胖子 老黑 还有丑鬼放了吧
So I'll be taking home the fat, the black, and the ugly.
这熊会说话 这熊会说话
It's a talking bear! It's a talking bear!
- 吼 - 这熊会说话 你们看到了 他的确能说话
- Growl. - It's a talking bear! No! No! You saw it! He was talking! He's a mother--
他说话了
He was talking!
哦 是蜜蜂 不要啊
Oh, no! Not the bees! Not the bees!
我的眼睛 我的眼睛
My eyes! My eyes!
准备享受生产的快乐吧
Here comes that bundle of joy.
这会是我生命中最美好的一天
This is gonna be the greatest day of my life.
恭喜啦
Congratulations.
你生出了一个2斤3两的肿瘤
You've given birth to a beautiful, 5-pound, 2-ounce tumor.
什么?
What?
这怎么可能?
But how is that possible?
估计是你压根就没怀孕吧
Hmm, I guess you never were pregnant.
我应该是把Ethel的卵巢囊肿放你肚子里了
I must have transferred an ovarian cyst from Ethel's body into yours,
当时以为是个胎儿呢
thinking it was an embryo.
那么超声检查还有婚检
What about the ultrasound and the checkups
和天拉维的基因测试是怎么回事?
And the Skymall dna test?
天拉维的产品全都是垃圾
Well, Skymall products are shit.
其他检测结果不准确是因为我嗑药嗑晕了
The rest are oversights that result from having your own prescription pad.
我要走了
Well, I'm out of here,
看我用天拉维的飞鼠服飞出去
Using my patented Skymall flying squirrel suit.
天拉维
Skymall!
好吧 我走了
All right. I'm leaving.
别急 这货要是个肿瘤 选择权在谁手里?
Wait. So if it was a tumor, whose choice was it?
你不知道 你不知道
You don't know. You don't know.
你不知道
You don't know.
说实话 我们都不知道
And none of us do, frankly.
堕胎是非常复杂的问题
Abortion is a very complicated issue.
谁特么在乎啊 我们不是要去猫头鹰餐厅的嘛
Oh, who gives a shit? I thought we were going to Hooters.
看来皆大欢喜了
Well, all's well that ends well.
- 我把这拿去当肉馅了 - 不要
- I'll go grind this into taco meat. - No!
我要留下它
I'm keeping it!
欢迎微博关注@漫迪字幕组
weibo.com/weheartcartoons